The Zamboni UP033
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Zamboni
1992 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP033
0.75 Linear Feet
1 Web sites
This collection contains issues of The Zamboni, a student-run journal of humor at Tufts, and web crawls documenting its web presence.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: The Zamboni and Web crawls.
Custodial History
These publications are picked up by DCA staff when they can get them.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of The Zamboni, a student-run journal of humor at Tufts, and web crawls documenting its web presence. It includes annual issues from 1992 through 2001, and more frequent issues since 2001.
- The Zamboni, 1992 -- 2021; UP033.001; 0.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of The Zamboni, a student-run journal of humor at Tufts.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Zamboni, 1992-10-07 -- 1994-09-20; UP033.001.001.00001 (Volume 1)
    Volume, issue
    IV, 1; VI, 1
    This file contains the October 7, 1992 issue and the September 20, 1994 issue of The Zamboni.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    The October 7, 1992 issue was donated by Alys Anne Wiedeke, 2019, accession UA-2019-069.
    newsprint
  - The Zamboni, 1994-11-01; UP033.001.001.00002 (Volume 1)
    VI, 2
  - The Zamboni, 1995-01-31; UP033.001.001.00003 (Volume 1)
    VI, 4
  - The Zamboni, 1995-02-28; UP033.001.001.00004 (Volume 1)
    VI, 5
  - The Zamboni, 1995-04-25; UP033.001.001.00005 (Volume 1)
    VI, 6
  - The Zamboni, 1995-09-19; UP033.001.001.00006 (Volume 1)
    VII, 1
  - The Zamboni, 1995-10-24; UP033.001.001.00007 (Volume 1)
    VII, 2
  - The Zamboni, 1995-12-05; UP033.001.001.00008 (Volume 1)
    VII, 3
  - The Zamboni, 1996-01-30; UP033.001.001.00009 (Volume 1)
    VII, 4
  - The Zamboni, 1996-02-27; UP033.001.001.00010 (Volume 1)
    VII, 5
  - The Zamboni, 1996-04-23; UP033.001.001.00011 (Volume 1)
    VII, 7
  - The Zamboni, 1996-09-17; UP033.001.001.00012 (Volume 1)
    VIII, 1
  - The Zamboni, 1996-10-16; UP033.001.001.00013 (Volume 1)
    VIII, 2
  - The Zamboni, 1997-02-04; UP033.001.001.00014 (Volume 1)
    VIII, 4
  - The Zamboni, 1997-03-04; UP033.001.001.00015 (Volume 1)
    VIII, 5
  - The Zamboni, 1997-04-10; UP033.001.001.00016 (Volume 1)
    VIII, 6
  - The Zamboni, 1997-09-30; UP033.001.001.00017 (Volume 1)
    IX, 1
  - The Zamboni, 1997-11-18; UP033.001.001.00018 (Volume 1)
    IX, 3
  - The Zamboni, 1998-02-04; UP033.001.001.00019 (Volume 1)
    IX, 4
  - The Zamboni, 1998-03-03; UP033.001.001.00020 (Volume 1)
    IX, 5
  - The Zamboni, 1998-04-07; UP033.001.001.00021 (Volume 1)
    IX, 6
  - The Zamboni, 1998-04-20; UP033.001.001.00022 (Volume 1)
    IX, 7
  - The Zamboni, 1998-09-22; UP033.001.001.00023 (Volume 1)
    X, 1
  - The Zamboni, 1998-10-20; UP033.001.001.00024 (Volume 1)
    X, 2
  - The Zamboni, 1998-11-10; UP033.001.001.00025 (Volume 1)
    X, 3
  - The Zamboni, 1999-02-23; UP033.001.001.00026 (Volume 1)
    X, 4
  - The Zamboni, 1999-03-16; UP033.001.001.00027 (Volume 1)
    X, 5
  - The Zamboni, 1999-04-20; UP033.001.001.00028 (Volume 1)
    X, 6
  - The Zamboni, 1999-05-04; UP033.001.001.00029 (Volume 1)
    X, 7
  - The Zamboni, 1999-10-05; UP033.001.001.00030 (Volume 1)
    XI, 1
  - The Zamboni, 1999-10-19; UP033.001.001.00031 (Volume 1)
    XI, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2000-04-08; UP033.001.001.00032 (Volume 1)
    XI, 7
  - The Zamboni, 2000-10-11; UP033.001.001.00033 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2000-11-06; UP033.001.001.00034 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2000-12-14; UP033.001.001.00035 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2001-02-26; UP033.001.001.00036 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2001-04-27; UP033.001.001.00037 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, "Vexations", 2001-04; UP033.001.001.00038 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2001-10-05; UP033.001.001.00039 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2001-12-13; UP033.001.001.00040 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2002-03-08; UP033.001.001.00041 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2002-04-19; UP033.001.001.00042 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2002-10-03; UP033.001.001.00043 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2002-11-06; UP033.001.001.00044 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2002-12-03; UP033.001.001.00045 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2003-02-21; UP033.001.001.00046 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2003-04-10; UP033.001.001.00047 (Volume 1)
    XIV, 5
  - The Zamboni, 2003-04-25; UP033.001.001.00048 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2003-10-03; UP033.001.001.00049 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2003-10-27; UP033.001.001.00050 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2003-12-05; UP033.001.001.00051 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2004-03-05; UP033.001.001.00052 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2004-04-16; UP033.001.001.00053 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2004-03 -- 2004-04; UP033.001.001.00054 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2004-10-15; UP033.001.001.00055 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2004-11-19; UP033.001.001.00056 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2004-12-10; UP033.001.001.00057 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2005-02-24; UP033.001.001.00058 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2005-04; UP033.001.001.00059 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2005-04-29; UP033.001.001.00060 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2005-10-07; UP033.001.001.00061 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2005-11-11; UP033.001.001.00062 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2005-12-09; UP033.001.001.00063 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2006-02-17; UP033.001.001.00064 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2006-04-28; UP033.001.001.00065 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2006-10-13; UP033.001.001.00066 (Volume 1)
    XVIII, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2006-11-10; UP033.001.001.00067 (Volume 1)
    XVIII, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2006-12-08; UP033.001.001.00068 (Volume 1)
    XVIII, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2007-02-26; UP033.001.001.00069 (Volume 1)
    XVIII, 4
  - The Zamboni, 2007-04-01; UP033.001.001.00070 (Volume 1)
    XVIII, 5
  - The Zamboni, 2007-04-27; UP033.001.001.00071 (Volume 1)
    XVIII, 6
  - The Zamboni, 2007-10-12; UP033.001.001.00072 (Volume 1)
    XIX, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2007-11-02; UP033.001.001.00073 (Volume 1)
    XIX, 2
  - The Zamboni "Zoobooks", 2008; UP033.001.001.00074 (Volume 1)
  - The Zamboni, 2008-04-04; UP033.001.001.00075 (Volume 1)
    XIX, 5
  - The Zamboni, 2008-04-25; UP033.001.001.00076 (Volume 1)
    XIX, 6
  - The Zamboni, 2008-10-10; UP033.001.001.00077 (Volume 1)
    XX, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2008-11-14; UP033.001.001.00078 (Volume 1)
    XX, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2008-12-01; UP033.001.001.00079 (Volume 1)
    XX, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2009-02-17; UP033.001.001.00080 (Volume 1)
    XX, 4
  - The Zamboni "Entertainment Weekly", 2009-04-04; UP033.001.001.00081 (Volume 1)
    XX, 5
  - The Zamboni, 2009-04-24; UP033.001.001.00082 (Volume 1)
    XX, 6
  - The Zamboni, 2009-10-17; UP033.001.001.00083 (Volume 1)
    XXI, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2009-11-16; UP033.001.001.00084 (Volume 1)
    XXI, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2009-12-12; UP033.001.001.00085 (Volume 1)
    XXI, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2010-02-28; UP033.001.001.00086 (Volume 1)
    XXI, 4
  - The Zamboni "American Wayz", 2010-04-04; UP033.001.001.00087 (Volume 1)
    XXI, 5
  - The Zamboni, 2010-04-25; UP033.001.001.00088 (Volume 1)
    XXI, 6
  - The Zamboni, 2010-10-15; UP033.001.001.00089 (Volume 1)
    XXII, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2010-11-12; UP033.001.001.00090 (Volume 1)
    XXII, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2010-12-03; UP033.001.001.00091 (Volume 1)
    XXII, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2011-02-18; UP033.001.001.00092 (Volume 1)
    XXII, 4
  - The Zamboni "Seventeen", 2011-04-08; UP033.001.001.00093 (Volume 1)
    XXII, 5
  - The Zamboni, 2011-10-21; UP033.001.001.00094 (Volume 1)
    XXIII, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2011-12-04; UP033.001.001.00095 (Volume 1)
    XXIII, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2012-03-05; UP033.001.001.00096 (Volume 1)
    XXIII, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2012-10-20; UP033.001.002.00001 (Volume 2)
    XXIV, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2012-11-17; UP033.001.002.00002 (Volume 2)
    XXIV, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2013-02-25; UP033.001.002.00003 (Volume 2)
    Volume
    XXIV
  - The Zamboni, 2013-11; UP033.001.002.00004 (Volume 2)
    XXV, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2014-03; UP033.001.002.00005 (Volume 2)
    XXV, 2
  - The Zamboni, 2014-04 -- 2014-05; UP033.001.002.00006 (Volume 2)
    XXV, 3
  - The Zamboni, Fall, 2014; UP033.001.002.00007 (Volume 2)
    25th Anniversary Issue
    XXVI, 1
  - The Zamboni, August, 2015; UP033.001.002.00008 (Volume 2)
    Reorientation 2015 Mini-issue
    XXVII, 1
  - The Zamboni Fall 2015, UP033.001.002.00009 (Volume 2)
  - The Zamboni, Winter, 2016; UP033.001.002.00010 (Volume 2)
    "40 and Loving It"
    XXVII, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2016-04-25; UP033.001.002.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2)
    Volume, Issue, Number
    XXVII, 5, 1
  - The Zamboni, 2016-04-27; UP033.001.002.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 12)
    XXVII, 5, 3
  - The Zamboni, 2016-04-28; UP033.001.002.0013; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2)
    XXVII, 5, 4
  - The Zamboni, 2016-04-29; UP033.001.002.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 14)
    XXVII, 5, 5
  - The Zamboni, "Orientation Mini-Issue", 2016-08; UP033.001.002.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 15)
    Volume, Number
    XXVIII, 1
  - The Zamboni, "The Burn Book: Emergency Election Issue", 2016-11; UP033.001.002.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 16)
    Volume, Issue
    XXVII, 2
  - The Zamboni, Spring, 2017; UP033.001.002.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 17)
    XXVIII, 4
  - The Zamboni, "Re-Orientation Issue", 2018-08; UP033.001.002.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 18)
    XXX, 1
  - The Zamboni, "Karen I Just Want to See My Bees Again You B- Issue", Spring 2019; UP033.001.002.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 2, Folder 19)
    XXX, 2
  - The Zamboni, "Re-Orientation Issue 2019", 2019 August; UP033.000123 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Zamboni, "On Probation", Fall 2019; UP033.000120 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    General
    XXXI, 2
  - The Zamboni, "Holidaze", 2019 December; UP033.000124 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Zamboni, "This issue is being recorded", November 2020; UP033.000121 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    XXXII, 2
  - The Zamboni, "The Adobe Flash Memorial Issue", Spring 2021; UP033.000122 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    XXXII, 3
  - The Zamboni, "Zamily Roadtrip", 2021 December; UP033.000125 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    V
    XXXIII, 3
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UP033.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Zamboni website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - The Zamboni, 2015 -- 2020; UP033.002.00001
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.